{
"question": "荷物",
"answer": "にもつ"
},
{
"question": "番号",
"answer": "ばんごう"
},
{
"question": "返す",
"answer": "かえす"
},
{
"question": "来年",
"answer": "らいねん"
},
{
"question": "明るい",
"answer": "あかるい"
},
{
"question": "近い",
"answer": "ちかい"
},
{
"question": "向こう",
"answer": "むこう"
},
{
"question": "始め",
"answer": "はじめ"
},
{
"question": "痛い",
"answer": "いたい"
},
{
"question": "休み",
"answer": "やすみ"
},
{
"question": "練習",
"answer": "れんしゅう"
},
{
"question": "十",
"answer": "じゅう"
},
{
"question": "上着",
"answer": "うわぎ"
},
{
"question": "先月",
"answer": "せんげつ"
},
{
"question": "結構",
"answer": "けっこう"
},
{
"question": "毎年",
"answer": "まいとし"
},
{
"question": "兄弟",
"answer": "きょうだい"
},
{
"question": "来月",
"answer": "らいげつ"
},
{
"question": "五",
"answer": "ご"
},
{
"question": "飲み物",
"answer": "のみもの"
},
